<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>dstbnnyfeed</title>
    <subtitle>blog and site updates for dustbunnybedroom :3c</subtitle>
    <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org" />
    <updated>2024-12-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/</id>
    <author>
        <name>jp</name>
        <email>dustbunny.bedroom@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    <entry>
        <title>dstbnnyblog: moving is weird</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-12-29" />
        <updated>2024-12-29T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-12-29</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>moving is weird</h1>
      <time datetime="2024-12-29">sunday, december 29, 2024</time>
      <p>
        around <time datetime="2024-08">August of 2024</time> i got the news
        that my family and i would have to be moving house around the end of the
        next month. it felt pretty sudden, honestly! (though i obviously won't
        be divulging into the details). we'd been living in that house for
        around 3-ish years and weren't expecting to have to move for at least a
        few more. we've spent a lot of time and effort making that house feel
        like our own; i spent a lot of time building up a creative space in my
        room (dubbed the "bnnystudio") that would let creating feel as fun and
        effortless as i could make it.
      </p>
      <figure>
        <img src="./2024-12-29/bnnystudio.jpg" alt="" />
        <figcaption>
          the last photo i took of the previous bnnystudio
        </figcaption>
      </figure>
      <p>
        but, of course, life happens and there's not much to do about it other
        than roll with the punches! i thought i'd put down a few experiences and
        thoughts on it:
      </p>
      <section>
        <h2>boxes</h2>
        <p>
          it's pretty cliché to say, but yeah, you really don't realize how much
          stuff you have until you have to put them all into fixed-size
          cardboard boxes. i always thought of myself as somebody that doesn't
          have a ton of superfluous stuff (i like finding ways of working with
          what i have, DIY 'til i die mindset!) but as it turns out, i
          apparently like to hold onto things: really old Christmas and birthday
          cards from people i haven't talked to in years, electronics that don't
          even really work but i swear i can figure out how to fix, literal,
          actual rocks. figuring out what's worth keeping and what isn't was a
          surprisingly a painful process, and not even because of whatever
          emotional attachment i have to these things, but just having to sift
          through the sheer amount of everything and figuring out where to start
          and stop, ADHD, executive dysfunction shenanigans, blah blah.
        </p>
        <p>
          one thing i didn't account for, stupidly lmao, was the weight that
          these boxes were going to be, as it was going to be <em>me</em>, my
          dad, and just a few family members and friends helping out and moving
          stuff into and out of a van. i never really thought about it in
          passing, but books? heavy. like, as fuck lol. i like keeping
          like-things together in the same space since it helps me with
          remembering where things are but that meant that i threw
          <em>all</em> of the books i owned into one box. same thing happened
          with all of the vinyl records our family's collected: all packed up in
          one box. and vinyl? heavy. as fuck.
        </p>
        <p>
          after having moved all of our boxes into the van we drove straight to
          the new place to immediately start moving them back out again. it's
          weird how annoying that felt, since this was the whole point, moving
          the stuff from here to there, but it kind of felt like we were undoing
          all the hard work of carrying things into the van and practicing
          Tetris-like skills to try and fit as much as possible in that space,
          in a funny, non-serious kind of way, of course.
        </p>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>ouchies</h2>
        <p>
          one thing about the new house itself is it's a bit more "stair-heavy"
          than our previous, and actually right at the front door there's
          already flight of stairs to get to the rest of the house. moving heavy
          boxes on their own is one thing, having to move them
          <em>up stairs</em> is definitely another. the feeling after it was all
          over and everything was now in the house was a weird mix of
          satisfaction and bittersweetness, like those scenes in movies where
          they say "welp! there's no going back now!"
        </p>
        <p>
          the days following were expectedly SORE. even though the initial day
          of arrival felt like such a success, there was still
          <em>a lot</em> more to do, because things in boxes have to eventually
          turn into things that are no longer in boxes, and some of those boxes
          would have to be brought up even more stairs to reach the rooms they
          were meant for. so i took a day off from school work to handle the
          brunt of this. my entire body hurt the whole time, but that was to be
          expected from all the work from the previous day—i'm not exactly the
          most active person in the world lol.
        </p>
        <p>
          turns out, days later, i got sick! probably from hauling boxes around
          in the rain (yeah, Mother Nature decided it was a good day to start
          raining lmao). moreover, in the following days where i started
          recovering from my sickness, i noticed that i was still feeling a very
          specific kind of pain in my leg, which was <em>very</em> apparent when
          walking down stairs. eventually, i learned that i had gotten IT band
          syndrome (yay!), most definitely from the strenuous activity from
          moving day, and especially because of the damn stairs lol. walking to
          and from classes on those days was quite the pain, and on days off i
          learned how to DIY an ice pack with a plastic bag, water, some rubbing
          alcohol to help along the healing process. maybe about 2–3 weeks later
          was when my leg became fully functional again, and i'd like to keep it
          that way from here on out lol; that period <em>sucked</em>.
        </p>
      </section>
      <section>
        <h2>moved in</h2>
        <p>
          it's been a full semester since having moved in now! i initially told
          myself that, while i'd be focusing more on my studies this time
          around, i'd still occasionally update this site and blog, but it looks
          like i'm
          <em>very</em> bad at multi-tasking lmao. i actually started writing
          this sometime last month but then got sidetracked. at the very least
          though, i did notice an improvement in academic performance and also a
          lot less stress from trying to juggle both creative projects
          <em>and</em> school work at the same time. i'll probably always be at
          least a little disappointed that i can't work on everything, always,
          and at the same time, but i think i'm learning to plan and prioritize
          a bit more.
        </p>
        <p>
          i'm bad at ending these types of "life update" posts lol. i hope
          <em>you're</em> doing well and that your holidays have been good!
          here's a demo i made in the time away from this site. take care!
        </p>
        <figure>
          <audio
            controls
            src="https://file.garden/ZhWP_IgEyxzXJSNb/sidewalk_idea_02.mp3"
          >
            <a
              rel="external"
              href="https://file.garden/ZhWP_IgEyxzXJSNb/sidewalk_idea_02.mp3"
              target="_blank"
              >listen here</a
            >
          </audio>
          <figcaption>sidewalk_idea_02.mp3</figcaption>
        </figure>
      </section>
      <footer>—jp</footer>
            ]]>
    </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>Casio SA-35 Decent Sampler instrument!</title>
        <summary>released my first sample instrument</summary>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#casio-sa-35" />
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#casio-sa-35</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[
          <p class="copy">
            a
            <a
              href="https://www.decentsamples.com/product/decent-sampler-plugin/"
              >Decent Sampler</a
            >
            instrument of all (except one) of the base tones on the Casio SA-35
            keyboard, also released by Radioshack as the Realistic
            Concertmate-470. i picked this keyboard up at a thrift store a
            couple of years ago and fell in love with it! it's super charming
            and nostalgic sounding. all the sounds were recorded DI using the
            provided headphone jack, the only processing done being some minor
            noise reduction to tame some noise/static.
          </p>
          <p class="copy">
            includes 24 presets in total. audio files are mono and in WAV format
            (48kHz, 24 bit).
          </p>
          <p class="copy">size: 205 MB</p>
          <ul class="list">
            <li class="list__item">
              <a
                rel="external"
                href="https://ko-fi.com/s/29d92b3d10"
                target="_blank"
                >download on Ko-fi</a
              >
            </li>
            <li class="list__item">
              <a
                rel="external"
                href="https://mega.nz/file/dT1GETRC#VpBmvdmN6lewTRhAboFztKmBw7X32ySOE39ue0mVrxs"
                target="_blank"
                >download on MEGA</a
              >
            </li>
          </ul>
            ]]>
    </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>accessibility!</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/accessibility" />
        <updated>2024-06-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/accessibility</id>
        <content type="text">
            added an accessibility statement to the site! it details the
            measures taken for accessibility as well as some of the current
            shortcomings that i plan on improving on! if you ever have any
            feedback to give regarding accessibility please feel free to share
            with me!
        </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>dstbnnyblog: end of may update</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-31" />
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-31</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hello again!</p>
    <p>
      i always feel like i should be updating this thing a little more often!
      the last couple of times i sat down to write one of these i stopped and
      wondered if what i'm writing about is, i guess, appropriate? in that, i
      wonder if i'm maybe putting too much of myself out there onto the
      internet? it's a thought that i find crosses my mind a lot more these
      days. i have a bit of a habit of oversharing sometimes, and if it were a
      few years ago i might not have really thought twice about it, but
      especially lately, i'm a bit more guarded about that stuff. and by
      oversharing i don't mean like private information, credit card numbers,
      addresses, and such lol, but more like intimate thoughts and details about
      your life, your struggles, etc.
    </p>
    <p>
      y'know, sometimes i'll come across a blog post on somebody's personal site
      and after reading it just sit there kind of dumbstruck and think, "huh, it
      kind of feels like i maybe shouldn't have read that", like i just walked
      in on some stranger by accident. i highly value being vulnerable in my
      creative expression&mdash;which i very much consider this site to
      be&mdash;but i also don't want to feel like that person that got walked in
      on with their pants down or something! there's probably a balance to be
      had, i'm just not exactly sure where the fulcrum point is. i just think my
      aversion to it is kind of interesting because a lot of my favourite art
      can be so painfully intimate, sometimes almost uncomfortably so, and i
      find that i connect with those a lot.
    </p>
    <p>
      i just check myself a lot on whether or not i'm approaching this in a
      healthy way. maybe that's a good thing or maybe i'm overthinking it all,
      idk! maybe i'll find out some day!
    </p>
    <hr />
    <p>
      other than my own self-imposed dilemmas about my online presence things
      haven't been <em>too</em> eventful lately. for the producers here, i
      recently released another
      <a href="/work/samples.html#smi-1460-voices">sample pack</a> i've been
      wanting to do for a while, and i've been getting a lot of fun ideas for
      more i could do that branch a bit away from recording dinky lil' toy
      instruments and stuff (as much as i love dinky lil' toy instruments)!
      currently, i'm trying to see if i can put together a sample library of one
      of those toy keyboards using
      <a
        rel="external"
        href="https://www.decentsamples.com/product/decent-sampler-plugin/"
        >Decent Sampler</a
      >
      (and maybe others if i can figure it out lol).
    </p>
    <p>
      feeling very happy with the progress on my own album that i've been slowly
      but regularly chipping away at! still in the writing stages but i like
      where it's going so far!
    </p>
    <p>
      trying to stretch every so often and gain some mobility back since i'm a
      little PC goblin (started practicing guitar standing up so i can at least
      spend that time standing more) (god, i would love a standing desk
      <span>:')</span>). picked up yo-yoing
      again after i stopped randomly last year (ADHD moment), it's been fun to
      fuck around with it in the times i take a break from the computer.
      unfortunately the yo-yo i was using somehow exploded lmao and now the two
      halves of it won't stay together for long (i get like two good throws out
      of it before it decides to fall apart again). it was a cheap one my mom
      got at an ice cream store a few years ago so it lived its life, already
      ordered a new one online
      <span>&gt;:3c</span>
    </p>
    <p>
      that's all for now! already have a plan for the next post which won't be a
      personal update but just some rambling about something that i think is
      neat! take care, i liked how our apple tree looked the other day so here:
    </p>
    <figure>
      <img
       
        src="./2024-05-31/apple-tree.jpg"
        alt="a blooming apple tree."
      />
    </figure>
    <footer>—jp</footer>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>new sample pack available! SMI-1460 electronic drum kit voices</title>
        <summary>released a new sample pack</summary>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#smi-1460-voices" />
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#smi-1460-voices</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[
        <p>voices from my SMI-1460 electronic drum kit that was handed down to me. included are two variations: DI through the two 1/4" jacks on the back, and through a normal IEC cassette tape with an Optimus CTR-117 cassette recorder. no processing was done other than a little EQ and normalisation.</p>
        <p>includes 430 WAV files (44.1kHz, 16bit), 215 voices with two variations each.</p>
        <p>size: 78.4MB</p>
        <ul>
            <li><a rel="external" href="https://ko-fi.com/s/e402fbfc50" target="_blank">download on Ko-fi</a></li>
            <li><a rel="external" href="https://mega.nz/file/IPcTBK7C#hNFj07DJvx3NEtJPifeL3_HKmLPNOapHwnZjKQOq2jY" target="_blank">download directly</a></li>

        </ul>
            ]]>
    </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>updated /now page (+ created this feed!)</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/now" />
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/now</id>
        <content type="text">
            i updated the media section of my /now page! and also created this
            feed! what makes it different from the site-log on the site? well, i
            plan to put blog posts here and also bigger updates, more-so site
            additions, while the site-log is going to continue being very
            granular in its content! stuff you'd probably want to be notified
            about and not, like, me fixing a dumb CSS mistake i missed a month
            ago lol.
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
