<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>dstbnnyfeed</title>
    <subtitle>blog and site updates for dustbunnybedroom :3c</subtitle>
    <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org" />
    <updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/</id>
    <author>
        <name>jp</name>
        <email>dustbunny.bedroom@gmail.com</email>
    </author>

    <entry>
        <title>Casio SA-35 Decent Sampler instrument!</title>
        <summary>released my first sample instrument</summary>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#casio-sa-35" />
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#casio-sa-35</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[
          <p class="copy">
            a
            <a
              href="https://www.decentsamples.com/product/decent-sampler-plugin/"
              >Decent Sampler</a
            >
            instrument of all (except one) of the base tones on the Casio SA-35
            keyboard, also released by Radioshack as the Realistic
            Concertmate-470. i picked this keyboard up at a thrift store a
            couple of years ago and fell in love with it! it's super charming
            and nostalgic sounding. all the sounds were recorded DI using the
            provided headphone jack, the only processing done being some minor
            noise reduction to tame some noise/static.
          </p>
          <p class="copy">
            includes 24 presets in total. audio files are mono and in WAV format
            (48kHz, 24 bit).
          </p>
          <p class="copy">size: 205 MB</p>
          <ul class="list">
            <li class="list__item">
              <a
                rel="external"
                href="https://ko-fi.com/s/29d92b3d10"
                target="_blank"
                >download on Ko-fi</a
              >
            </li>
            <li class="list__item">
              <a
                rel="external"
                href="https://mega.nz/file/dT1GETRC#VpBmvdmN6lewTRhAboFztKmBw7X32ySOE39ue0mVrxs"
                target="_blank"
                >download on MEGA</a
              >
            </li>
          </ul>
            ]]>
    </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>accessibility!</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/accessibility" />
        <updated>2024-06-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/accessibility</id>
        <content type="text">
            added an accessibility statement to the site! it details the
            measures taken for accessibility as well as some of the current
            shortcomings that i plan on improving on! if you ever have any
            feedback to give regarding accessibility please feel free to share
            with me!
        </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>dstbnnyblog: end of may update</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-31" />
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/posts/2024-05-31</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>hello again!</p>
    <p>
      i always feel like i should be updating this thing a little more often!
      the last couple of times i sat down to write one of these i stopped and
      wondered if what i'm writing about is, i guess, appropriate? in that, i
      wonder if i'm maybe putting too much of myself out there onto the
      internet? it's a thought that i find crosses my mind a lot more these
      days. i have a bit of a habit of oversharing sometimes, and if it were a
      few years ago i might not have really thought twice about it, but
      especially lately, i'm a bit more guarded about that stuff. and by
      oversharing i don't mean like private information, credit card numbers,
      addresses, and such lol, but more like intimate thoughts and details about
      your life, your struggles, etc.
    </p>
    <p>
      y'know, sometimes i'll come across a blog post on somebody's personal site
      and after reading it just sit there kind of dumbstruck and think, "huh, it
      kind of feels like i maybe shouldn't have read that", like i just walked
      in on some stranger by accident. i highly value being vulnerable in my
      creative expression&mdash;which i very much consider this site to
      be&mdash;but i also don't want to feel like that person that got walked in
      on with their pants down or something! there's probably a balance to be
      had, i'm just not exactly sure where the fulcrum point is. i just think my
      aversion to it is kind of interesting because a lot of my favourite art
      can be so painfully intimate, sometimes almost uncomfortably so, and i
      find that i connect with those a lot.
    </p>
    <p>
      i just check myself a lot on whether or not i'm approaching this in a
      healthy way. maybe that's a good thing or maybe i'm overthinking it all,
      idk! maybe i'll find out some day!
    </p>
    <hr />
    <p>
      other than my own self-imposed dilemmas about my online presence things
      haven't been <em>too</em> eventful lately. for the producers here, i
      recently released another
      <a href="/work/samples.html#smi-1460-voices">sample pack</a> i've been
      wanting to do for a while, and i've been getting a lot of fun ideas for
      more i could do that branch a bit away from recording dinky lil' toy
      instruments and stuff (as much as i love dinky lil' toy instruments)!
      currently, i'm trying to see if i can put together a sample library of one
      of those toy keyboards using
      <a
        rel="external"
        href="https://www.decentsamples.com/product/decent-sampler-plugin/"
        >Decent Sampler</a
      >
      (and maybe others if i can figure it out lol).
    </p>
    <p>
      feeling very happy with the progress on my own album that i've been slowly
      but regularly chipping away at! still in the writing stages but i like
      where it's going so far!
    </p>
    <p>
      trying to stretch every so often and gain some mobility back since i'm a
      little PC goblin (started practicing guitar standing up so i can at least
      spend that time standing more) (god, i would love a standing desk
      <span>:')</span>). picked up yo-yoing
      again after i stopped randomly last year (ADHD moment), it's been fun to
      fuck around with it in the times i take a break from the computer.
      unfortunately the yo-yo i was using somehow exploded lmao and now the two
      halves of it won't stay together for long (i get like two good throws out
      of it before it decides to fall apart again). it was a cheap one my mom
      got at an ice cream store a few years ago so it lived its life, already
      ordered a new one online
      <span>&gt;:3c</span>
    </p>
    <p>
      that's all for now! already have a plan for the next post which won't be a
      personal update but just some rambling about something that i think is
      neat! take care, i liked how our apple tree looked the other day so here:
    </p>
    <figure>
      <img
       
        src="./2024-05-31/apple-tree.jpg"
        alt="a blooming apple tree."
      />
    </figure>
    <footer>—jp</footer>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>new sample pack available! SMI-1460 electronic drum kit voices</title>
        <summary>released a new sample pack</summary>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#smi-1460-voices" />
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/samples#smi-1460-voices</id>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[
        <p>voices from my SMI-1460 electronic drum kit that was handed down to me. included are two variations: DI through the two 1/4" jacks on the back, and through a normal IEC cassette tape with an Optimus CTR-117 cassette recorder. no processing was done other than a little EQ and normalisation.</p>
        <p>includes 430 WAV files (44.1kHz, 16bit), 215 voices with two variations each.</p>
        <p>size: 78.4MB</p>
        <ul>
            <li><a rel="external" href="https://ko-fi.com/s/e402fbfc50" target="_blank">download on Ko-fi</a></li>
            <li><a rel="external" href="https://mega.nz/file/IPcTBK7C#hNFj07DJvx3NEtJPifeL3_HKmLPNOapHwnZjKQOq2jY" target="_blank">download directly</a></li>

        </ul>
            ]]>
    </content>
    </entry>

    <entry>
        <title>updated /now page (+ created this feed!)</title>
        <link href="https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/now" />
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
        <id>https://dustbunnybedroom.neocities.org/now</id>
        <content type="text">
            i updated the media section of my /now page! and also created this
            feed! what makes it different from the site-log on the site? well, i
            plan to put blog posts here and also bigger updates, more-so site
            additions, while the site-log is going to continue being very
            granular in its content! stuff you'd probably want to be notified
            about and not, like, me fixing a dumb CSS mistake i missed a month
            ago lol.
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
